Tweet-tweet! One, two, march!
Stomp like an elephant, heavy and big,
Oink like a little pink muddy pig!
Swing like a monkey from tree to tree,
High in the jungle as wild and free!
Puppy goes woof-woof, kitty goes meow,
Let’s make all the animal noises now!
March, march, march through the jungle green,
The happiest animals you've ever seen!
Wiggle your tail and flap your wings,
Listen as the jungle choir sings!
Hop like a bunny across the grass,
Watch the tall yellow giraffes pass!
Roar like a lion, proud and brave,
Give a friendly penguin friend a wave!
Duck goes quack-quack,
frog goes ribbit-ribbit,
Jump in the pond and splash a little bit!
March, march, march through the jungle green,
The happiest animals you've ever seen!
Wiggle your tail and flap your wings,
Listen as the jungle choir sings! Roar! Quack! Meow!
Drum roll and crash cymbal